Mss.Ms.Coll.56
American Philosophical Society
- XII. Journal, 1922; 1931-2003; undated; 3.0 Linear feet 12 vols.
  - [Journal, Volume 12], 1997 March 27-2003 September 20; 1.0 vol. (Box 45)
    Post-type binder with animal-motif endpapers apparently hand-painted; no title on binder, no title-page.
  - [Journal, Volume 12] Contents of envelope inside rear cover. Folder 1, 1974 January 8-2003 December; undated (Box 45)
    Ephemera, photos, and corespondence.
  - [Journal, Volume 12] Contents of envelope inside rear cover. Folder 2, 1933-1988; undated (Box 45)
    Photos.
  - [Journal, Volume 12] Contents of envelope inside rear cover. Folder 3, 1934 October-2003 December 7; undated (Box 45)
    Ephemera, photos, and correspondence.
  - [Journal, Volume 12] Contents of envelope inside rear cover. Folder 4, 1954 May; 1992 April 9 (Box 45)
    [1] Crayon drawing of Leopold backyard, by young Madelyn Leopold, May 1954. [2] Watercolor, "Isla Magdalena Apr 9 92 Santa Margarita", by Luna Leopold.
- XIII. Manuscripts, 1.0 Linear feet
  Series XIII comprises manuscripts and some drafts of published materials by Leopold. Listings in quotation marks are Leopold's own folder titles or manuscript titles; others are descriptive based on Leopold's folder label and contents.
  See "Works By Others" (Series XV) for manuscript materials written by other individuals. Also see "Leopold Family Papers" for some materials written by members of his family.
  A few manuscripts have been bound into Leopold's bound set of published works (see Series XIV, Subseries 1).
  - "A Microcosm of Climatic Change", 2003 October 10 (Box 46)
    "A proposed chapter or section in the mms on Solar changes."
  - "A Value in Fear", 2000 (Box 46)
    Original manuscript with comments by Alan E. Watson. File includes correspondence with Watson, Alan E., 2000 January 27, March 7, March 30.
  - "A View of the River" (Box 46)
    File contains only: [1] Photographs from envelope marked, "Jacket Art Possibilities". [2] Blue-line position prints of illustrations. [3] Review of "A View of the River" by S.S., in "Investigación y Ciencia" (January 1997, p. 91) [in Spanish].
  - "Archaeological Trash", by Luna B. Leopold and Claudio Vita-Finzi, 2003 October 10 (Box 46)
    "Oct 10 03 Final". File includes photographs, negatives, and original illustrations.
    File includes manuscript: "Clovis, Pre-Clovis, Climate Change, and Extinction" by C. Vance Haynes, Jr., [1998].
    File includes correspondence: Vita-Finzi, Claudio, undated. Wendorf, Fred, 2000 May 22.
  - "Attributes of an Alluvial River and Their Relation to Water Policy and Management" by William Thrush, Scott McBain, and Luna B. Leopold. First Draft, 2000 May 15; undated (Box 46)
  - Braided Rivers Manuscript, November 1985, 1985 November (Box 46)
    Folder title and date as filed by Leopold. Contains manuscript, "Some Relations Among Velocity, Depth, and Slope in Braided Rivers". File includes photographs.
    See also Oversize Box 1, Folder 7.
  - Colorado River Manuscript, Lake Powell 1994 (Box 46)
    Folder title and date as filed by Leopold. Contains manuscript: "Reservoir as Base Level--Effect on Sediment Deposit".
    File includes correspondence: Bull, William B. to Dickinson, William R., 1994 December 15. Bull, William B. to Leopold, Luna B., 1994 December 15; 1995 February 15. Dickinson, William R. to Bull, William B., undated (November 21). Lucchitta, Ivo to Leopold, Luna B., 1996 March 26.
  - "The Erosion Problem of Southwestern United States" by Luna B. Leopold [Ph.D. dissertation, Harvard University], 1950 April; 1.0 vol. (Box 46)
    Bound carbon copy; original photographs laid in.
  - "Flood Control: Policy and Performance", 1998 (Box 46)
    Manuscript, and reviewers' comments for paper published in "Journal of the American Water Resources Association".
  - "Floods and Sandbars in the Grand Canyon" by Ivo Lucchitta and Luna B. Leopold (Box 46)
    Two drafts, heavily edited.
  - "Flutters High the Hawk: Sonnets and other poems by Luna B. Leopold 1932-1993", undated (Box 46)
    Printed copy (self-produced?); comb-bound. [29] leaves.
  - "Genre of the Journal", 1999 (Box 46)
  - "Geomorphic Effects of Urbanization in 41 Years of Observation" by Luna B. Leopold, Reed Huppman, and Andrew Miller, 1994-2005 (Box 47)
    Manuscript published by "Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society" (APS).
    File includes photograph and data sheets for Watts Branch, Maryland.
    File includes manuscript: "Riverbed Rocks: How They Break" by Luna B. Leopold (draft 2000 October), [2] p.
    File includes correspondence: Babbitt, Susan (APS) to Leopold, Luna B., 2005 August 26. Huppman, Reed to Leopold, Luna B., 1995 March 4. Leopold, Luna B., to Babbitt, Susan (APS), 2005 August 1. Leopold, Luna B. to Huppman, Reed, undated. Leopold, Luna B. to Miller, Andrew J., 1995 March 3. Miller, Andrew J. to Leopold, Luna B., 1994 May 6, 1995 February 23, 2000 April 30. Miller, Andrew J. to Schmidt, Jack [Schmidt, John C.], 2005 October 8. Miller, Andrew J. to Wolman, Reds [Wolman, M. Gordon], 2005 October 11. Schmidt, Jack [Schmidt, John C.] to City Manager, Rockville, Maryland, 2005 October 7. Wilcock, Peter to Straus, Susan, 2005 October 29.
    See also Extra-Oversize, Series XIII: Rockville, Maryland quadrangle; annotated with a grid in the Watts Branch area.
  - "Geomorphology and Science Needs", undated (Box 47)
    [5] leaves. Perhaps draft of an address.
  - Hawaiian Paper, undated (Box 47)
    Contains manuscript: "Short Term Climatic Changes as Mimics of Major Events" by Claudio Vita-Finzi and Luna B. Leopold.
    File includes correspondence: Vita-Finzi, Claudio, [2000]; 2003 May 20, 24.
  - Lake Manuscript Drafts (Box 47)
    Folder title and date as filed by Leopold. Contains manuscript: "Temperature Profiles and Bathymetry of Some High Mountain Lakes", with review comments by Terry Svalberg and Ted Porwoll. Second manuscript of same title, with review comments by Dave Clow, 2000. Partial third manuscript with review comments by Chip L. Rawlins. Fourth manuscript, largely unmarked.
    File includes correspondence: Clow, David, 2000 March 14. Rawlins, C. L., 2000 March 27. Svalberg, Terry, and Porwoll, Ted, 2000 April 10.
  - Lake Manuscript Final, 1986-2000 (Box 47)
    Contains manuscript: "Temperature Profiles and Bathymetry of Some High Mountain Lakes" [re: "Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences", Vol. 97, No. 12 (2000 June 6), p. 6267-6270].
    File includes: "Water Monitoring Record, Acid Deposition Study" data sheets, 1986-1992; correspondence and information relating to "Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences"; corrected page proofs; and printout of paper from "PNAS Online", printed 2000 June 12.
  - "Learning From the River" by Luna B. Leopold and David L. Rosgen, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
    "ms for invited paper Conference on Designing for Natural Channel systems, Ontario, Canada, March 3-4,1994".
    File includes correspondence: Breton, Hazel, 1993 June 3, August 20. Miller, David, 1993 August 29. Rosgen,David L., [1993].
  - "Let Rivers Teach Us" (Box 47)
    Manuscript and corrected galley proof.
  - "On the Dates of Valley Erosion" by Luna B. Leopold and Claudio Vita-Finzi, undated (Box 47)
    Original folder tab labelled,"C14 dates--Vita-Finzi & LBL".
    File includes correspondence: "B.T." [Ben Travato; pseudonym of Vita-Finzi, Claudio] to Leopold, undated.
  - Open letter in re Mississippi River Floods, undated (Box 47)
  - Penrose Medal Response (draft) (Box 47)
  - "The River Program", undated (Box 47)
    Letter in re the establishment of "a school or a training program that would allow interested individuals to associate with the experience dmembes of the community who have dealt with rivers... ."
  - "Riverbed Rocks: How They Break", 2000 October (Box 47)
    Corrected draft.
  - "The Sale of Rectitude", 1995, 1997 (Box 47)
    Manuscript in re ethics in resource management and peer review, [1997]; declined by "Science".
    File includes corresondence: "Science", 1997 May 28. Stahl, Andy, 1995 October 31.
  - "Science". Hydrograph Component Analysis, 2002 (Box 47)
    Folder title as given by Leopold. Includes outline for paper and manuscript, "The Effect of Dams and a Strategy for Reducing the Damage" by William J. Trush and Luna B. Leopold; appended to correspondence to Trush, 2002 May 18
  - "Science". "Luna Leopold Science Paper 2002", 2000-2002 (Box 47)
    Correspondence, notes, and manuscript, "The Effect of Dams and a Strategy for Reducing the Damage" by William J. Trush and Luna B. Leopold; edited to "A Strategy for Reducing the Ecological Damage of Dams" by Luna B. Leopold and William J. Trush.
    File includes correspondence: Leopold, Luna B. to McBain, Scott, and Trush, William J., 2000 February 23.
  - "Some Observations Concerning Early Man in Sublette County, Wyoming", 2000 August (Box 47)
    Fragment, 1 p. "For discussion, not for publication".
  - "Trials, Drafts, Reminders", 2005; undated (Box 47)
    Miscellaneous drafts, fragments, and notes. Includes: [1] "Why Can't America Hear?" [2] "Meanders". [3] List of bird names. [4] Printed copy of "History and Future of the Bekerley Waterfront. Walk led by Susan Schwartz, Friends of Five Creek[s]", undated. [5] Other notes.
  - "USFS Report", [2005] (Box 47)
    In re scientifically based framework for allocating instream flows, report to U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service. This copy printed 2005 December 11.
  - Watts Branch, Maryland, 2000; [2005] (Box 47)
    Includes corrected manuscript: "Geomorphic Effects of Urbanization in 41 years of observation" by Luna B. Leopold, Reed Huppman, and Andrew Miller, revision [2005] April 1. Includes photographs, data sheets.
    File includes correspondence: Miller, Andrew, 2000 May 19.
- XIV. Works By Luna B. Leopold, 2.0 Linear feet 8 vols., 2 boxes
  Series XIV comprises the published writings of Luna Leopold and occasional manuscript and related materials. (See Series XIII for the bulk of Leopold's manuscript materials.)
  Subseries 1 is a series of eight volumes bound by Leopold, containing in chronological sequence his published papers between 1939 and 2003. He has in some cases bound into the sequence manuscript materials or pertinent notes. Each volume contains a bibiographical listing that embraces the volume contents.
  Subseries 2 is a set of offprints and photocopies of Leopold papers that are not included within the bound set in Subseries 1.
  Subseries 3 is a box containing separate volumes that were published by Leopold, which of course are not included in the bound set in Subseries 1.
  - 1. Works By Luna B. Leopold. Bound Collection, 8.0 vols.
    Subseries 1 is a series of eight volumes hand-bound by Leopold, containing in chronological sequence his published papers between 1939 and 2003. Volume containing Nos. 103-142 is absent; not received by APS. He has occasionally bound in manuscript materials or pertinent notes like items of correspondence. Each volume contains a bibiographical listing that embraces the volume contents, but which also indicates items that were omitted from the bound set either due to unavailability or size. Items noted by Leopold as absent from the bound volumes may or may not be included in Subseries 2, "Works By Luna B. Leopold Not Included in Bound Collection", or Subseries 3, "Works By Luna B. Leopold As Separate Volumes". All items are as received from Leopold.
    See also Series XIII, Manuscripts, for some titles by Leopold that are annotated copies of working or finished drafts of published works.
    - "Leopold on Climate. Papers 1942-1952.", 1.0 vol. (Volume 1)
      Thirteen papers relating to climatology and paleoclimates in the American Southwest, and climatology in Hawaii.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 1-25", 1939-1949; 1.0 vol. (Volume 2)
      Published papers and manuscript data, 1939-1949.
      Includes carbon copy of typewritten mansucript, "The Annual Rainfall of East Maui. A Report to the U.S. Geological Survey and East Maui Irrigation Company", Department of Meteorology, Pineapple Research Institute, and Experiment Station, Hawaiian Sugar Planters' Assoc., Honolulu, Hawaii, August 1949; title-page annotated by Leopold, "Published in Planter's Record date?" [i.e., Pineapple Research Institute of Hawaii, Technical Paper 189, "Hawiian Planters Record", Vol. 53, No. 2 (1949)].
      Includes mimeographed report: "Relation of Watershed Condition to Flood Discharge: A Theoretical Analysis", U.S. Soil Conservation Service, Southwest Region, Regional Bulletin No. 57, Water Conservation and Management Series, No. 2 (1939 August 1). Has appended to it Leopold's original manuscript data sheets, "Assumptions For Computation of Hydrograph for Typical Area on Rio Puerco", and hydrograph data.
      Volume uses topographic maps of Santa Fe, New Mexico, for endpapers.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 27-56", 1950-1958; 1.0 vol. (Volume 3)
      Published papers, 1950-1958.
      Includes typescript: "The Erosion Problem of the Southwest" (Ph.D. dissertation, Harvard University), to which is appended memoranda and review comments by Brown, Carl, 1951 July 19, and Vanoni, Vito A., 1951 August 9.
      Not included in the bibliographical list in front of volume is a copy of the November 1958 issue of "Sierra Club Bulletin", bound in at end, in which two pertinent papers are published: "Conservation--And Tinkering", by Aldo Leopold, p. 31 [excerpt from "Round River" (Oxford, 1953)]; and "Water in the Conservation Movement", by Luna Leopold, p. 32-40.
      Volume uses topographic maps of vicinity of Seneca Creek, Maryland, for endpapers.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 57-80", 1950-1958; 1.0 vol. (Volume 4)
      Not included in the bibliographical list in front of volume is a copy of "Water, Industry, and Myth", a "speech given by Luna B. Leopold... at the National Water Conference, Sheraton-Park Hotel, Washington, D.C., December 8-9,1965" [bound between 1960 item nos. 64/65].
      No. 80, "Water" by Leopold and Helene L. Baldwin, is a young-reader title.
      Volume uses topographic maps of vicinity of Edgemont Lake, Bridger National Forest, Wyoming, for endpapers.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 81-102", 1962-1966; 1.0 vol. (Volume 5)
      Published papers, 1962-1966.
      No. 81, "Government Responsibility for Land and Water: Guardian or Developer?" by Leopold and Raymond L. Nace, is a carbon-copy of typescript for the published paper.
      Volume uses topographic maps of vicinity of New Fork River, Wyoming, for endpapers.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 143-164", 1964-1993; 1.0 vol. (Volume 6)
      Published papers, 1964-1993.
      No. 146, "Natural Morphology--Key to Stream Channel Stability" by Leopold and David L. Rosgen, contains editorial markings dated 1988 September 19-20, by [name illegible].
      Between nos 148/149 is a photocopy of an edited manuscript, "Reading Landscape" by Leopold; undated.
      Included near end of volume is copy of manuscript, "Flutters the High Hawk: Sonnets and Poems by Luna B. Leopold 1932-1993", to which is appended correspondence: Leopold, Niki, 1993 September 30.
      Volume uses topographic maps of vicinity of Arlington and Winchester, Massachusetts, for endpapers.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 165-182", 1949; 1981; 1990-1997; 1.0 vol. (Volume 7)
      No. 180, "The Sale of Rectitude", is an edited manuscript.
    - "Writings of Luna B. Leopold. Nos. 182 [183]-196", 1997-2003; 1.0 vol. (Volume 8)
      Nos. 195 ("A Microcosm of Climatic Change", 2003) and 196 ("Archaeological Trash" by Leopold and Claudio Vita-Finzi, 2003), are manuscripts.
  - 2. Works By Luna B. Leopold Not Included in Bound Set, 1967-1992; 1.0 box (Box 48)
    No separate listing. May not be included in Leopold's main lists of publications.
  - 3. Works By Luna B. Leopold as Separate Volumes, 1.0 box
    - "The Colorado River Region and John Wesley Powell" (U.S. Geological Survey Professional Paper 669, 1969); including Chapter D, "The Rapids and the Pools--Grand Canyon", by Leopold., 1.0 vol. (Box 49)
    - "The Hydraulic Geometry of Stream Channels and Some Physiographic Implications" by Leopold and Thomas Maddock, Jr. (U.S. Geological Survey Professional Paper 252, 1953)., 1.0 vol. (Box 49)
    - "Hydrology, Geomorphology, and Environmental Policy: U.S. Geological Survey, 1950-1972, and UC Berkeley, 1972-1987", 1990-1991; 1.0 vol. (Box 49)
      Oral-history interview conducted by Ann Lage, 1990-1991; with an Introduction by Thomas Dunne. University of California at Berkeley, The Bancroft Library, Regional Oral History Office, [xii], viii, 309 [313] p. Bound volume.
      Related ephemera that was found in this volume has been removed to a separate folder (following).
    - "Hydrology, Geomorphology, and Environmental Policy: U.S. Geological Survey, 1950-1972, and UC Berkeley, 1972-1987". Related Ephemera., 1992-1994 (Box 49)
      Ephemera removed from inside bound volume of oral-history interview with Leopold, "Hydrology, Geomorphology, and Environmental Policy: U.S. Geological Survey, 1950-1972, and UC Berkeley, 1972-1987".
    - "Physiographic and Hydraulic Studies of River, 1956-61" (U.S. Geological Survey Professional Paper 282, 1961); containing several papers coauthored by Leopold., 1.0 vol. (Box 49)
- XV. Works By Others, 1.25 Linear feet 2 boxes
  Series XV comprises works written by other writers than Leopold. The material that is contained here includes volumes or offprints that were in some fashion annotated or marked by Leopold. The series includes some manuscript materials. Two special collections (those of Walter B. Langbein and Claudio Vita-Finzi, both long-time colleagues and coauthors with Leopold) include mostly complete collections of these authors' works, as assembled by Leopold.
  See also Series VI, Leopold Family Papers, which includes works written by immediate members of the Leopold family.
  - Anonymous. "Proposal For a White Paper on the Bureau of Reclamation and Western Water Policies", undated (Box 50)
    Manuscrpt. 7 p.
  - Baron, Jill. "Precipitation and Lake Chemical composition in the Wind River Mountains of Wyoming: Analysis of U.S. Forest Service and NADP Data Sets. A report submitted to the USDA Forest Service, Bridger Teton National Forest", 1996 March 1 (Box 50)
    "A version was submitted to Water Resources Research in July 1996, with Kurt Nelson, Ann Mebane, and A. Galbraith as co-authors."
  - Dawdy, David R. "The Need To Consider the IMpacts of Global Warming on Hetch Hetchy"., 2004 August 10 (Box 50)
    Manuscript, "Draft to 8/10/2004".
  - Interagency Floodplain Management Review Committee. "Sharing the Challenge: Floodplain Managment Into the 21st Century. A Blueprint for Change [Part 1]" (Report to the Administration Floodplain Management Task Force, Washington, D.C., June 1994), 1994 June; 1.0 vol. (Box 50)
    Copy annotated by Leopold.
  - Interagency Floodplain Management Review Committee. "Sharing the Challenge: Floodplain Managment Into the 21st Century. A Blueprint for Change, Part V. (Report to the Administration Floodplain Management Task Force, Washington, D.C., June 1994), 1994 June; 1.0 vol. (Box 50)
  - Langbein, Walter B. "Principal Papers by Walter B. Langbein, 1938-1967", 1.0 vol. (Box 50)
    Leopold's assembled and bound collection; all are photocopies.
  - Maddock, Thomas, Jr., [1975] (Box 50)
    Draft manuscript, edited, untitled, [1975], in re "hydraulics of alluvial streams and the transport of sediment in alaluvial channels"; with mansucript data sheets by Leopold. Accompanied by correspondence, Tom [Maddock, Thomas, Jr.] to Leopold, 1975 May 19.
  - Moody, Thomas O., and Odem, Wilbert. "Regional Relationships for Bankfull Stage in Natural Channels of Central and Southern Arizona. Final Report." (Northern Arizona University, College of Engineering and Technology, February 1999) (Box 51)
    Report prepared for U.S. Forest Service and Arizona Department of Environmental Quality. Accompanied by cover letter from Odem, Wilbert, to Leopold, 1999 September 27.
  - Riley, Ann, and Spencer, Mark. "Project Report. Teaching Environmental Restoration[:] Locally-based restoration centers as university classrooms." [1998 Fall], undated (Box 51)
    Manuscript, undated. Accompanied by cover letter from Riley, Ann to Leopold, 2000 February 21, which notes she wrote "with a Berkeley grad student on the field course you helped us with in the Fall of 1998. It will be published in the summer edition of 'Ecological Restoration Journal.'"
  - Scheidegger, A. E., and Langbein, W. B. "Probability Concepts in Geomorphology" (U.S. Geological Survey Professional Paper 500-C, 1966) (Box 51)
    Contains annotations by Leopold.
  - Smith, W. O., Vetter, C. P., Cummings, G. B., and others. "Comprehensive Survey of Sedimentation in Lake Mead, 1948-49" (U.S. Geological Survey Professional Paper 295, 1960), 1.0 vol. (Box 51)
    A water-damaged copy. With notation by Tim Hannon, U.S. Geological Survey, Denver, dated 1996 April 4: "Glad the book is desired and appreciated."
  - Symposium: "Glen Canyon Dam Beach/Habitat-Building Flow: Abstracts and Executive Summaries, April 1997" (no imprint), 1997 April; 1.0 vol. (Box 51)
    With occasional annoations and markings by Leopold.
  - Tichenor, Jerome. "Poems in Contempt of Progress", edited by Joel W. Hedgpeth (The Boxwood Press, Pacific Grove, California, 1974), 1.0 vol. (Box 51)
    Inscribed to Leopold by Joel [Hedgpeth], 1994 June 20.
  - Vita-Finzi, Claudio, 1965-1995; undated (Box 51)
    Leopold's collection of papers by frequent coauthor and correspondent, Claudio Vita-Finzi. Includes manuscript: "Mediaeval Mud and the Maunder Minimum" (annotated by Vita-Finzi, "Bologna Mar 93").
  - Wallace, David Rains. "The Deer and the Wolf: Aldo Leopold's Ecological Vision", 1987 March (Box 51)
    Manuscript, submitted to "Sierra"; accompanied by cover letter from the Associate Editor of "Sierra" requesting Leopold to review, 1987 April 2.
  - Woo, Lisa. "Reflection on "A Sand County Almanac", 2000 November 1 (Box 51)
    A class paper for "ES 140". 3 p.
- XVI. Aerial Photographs of Canyonbound Rivers, 1964-1965; 2.0 Linear feet 6 boxes; 818 photos
  Series XVI comprises standard 9- or 10-inch square aerial photographs taken by the U.S. Geological Survey on systematic overflights of several canyonbound rivers in the American West in 1964 and 1965. These were used in Leopold's researches on these rivers: Colorado River, Utah; San Juan River, Utah; Colorado River, Arizona (Marble and Grand Canyons). [The Green River of Utah, also studied by Leopold, is not represented in these photo sets.] These 818 photographs were disorganized when received by APS. The collection was broken down into geographically defined groups by processing archivist Earle Spamer, who is familiar with these rivers. Within each group the enumeration of photos (as automatically stamped on them during flight) is sequential; hiatuses are noted.
  - Group 1. Colorado River, Utah. Moab, Utah, to confluence of Green River, 1964 June 19, July 1 (Box 52)
    161 photos; 1964 June 19, July 1
  - Group 2. San Juan River, Utah. To confluence of Colorado River, 1965 April 21-22 (Box 53)
    236 photos; 1965 April 21-22
  - Group 3. Colorado River, Arizona. Marble Canyon. Lees Ferry to confluence of Little Colorado River (Mile -0.1 to 63.0), 1965 May 14 (Box 54)
    118 photos; 1965 May 14
  - Group 4. Colorado River, Arizona. Grand Canyon. Confluence of Little Colorado River to 209 Mile Rapid (Mile 61.9 to 209.5), 1965 May 14, 18 (Box 55)
    218 photos; 1965 May 14, 18
  - Group 5. Colorado River, Arizona. Marble Canyon-Grand Canyon (Soap Creek to Tapeats Creek, Miles ca. 11.4-135.0), 1965 June 2 (Box 56)
    73 photos; 1965 June 2